const quiz2data = [
    {
      question: "George failed ___ the final exam.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to pass", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "passing", isCorrect: false},
     ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: fail, hope, pretend, start, agree, consent, decide etc. '
   },
    {
      question: "I like ___ the guitar.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to play", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "playing", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Verbs of liking and disliking such as: enjoy, hate, fancy, like, love etc are followed by the -ing form.'
   },
    {
      question: "I can't play a musical instrument, but I'd like to learn ___ the piano.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to play", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "playing", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: learn, fail, hope, pretend, start, agree, consent, decide etc.'
   },
    {
      question: "I wish my dog would stop ___ every time someone knocks my door.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to bark", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "barking", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: stop, finish, imagine, suggest, recommend, avoid, mind, miss, risk, enjoy.'
   },
    {
      question: "My sister refused ___ with me.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to come", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "coming", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: refuse, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
   },
    {
      question: "I was very hungry, so my friend suggested ___ dinner early.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "having", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "to have", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: suggest, stop, recommend, admit, avoid, imagine, finish, consider, deny, risk, fancy etc'
   },
    {
      question: "I couldn't afford ___ in New York. It's too expensive.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to live", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "living", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: afford, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
   },
    {
      question: "Don't forget ___ with you the money for the rent.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "bringing", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "to bring", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: afford, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
   },
    {
      question: "My brother avoids ___ dinner too late.", 
      answersList: [
        {answer: "having", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "to have", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: avoid, recommend, admit, stop, imagine, finish, consider, deny, risk, fancy etc'
    },
    {
      question: "James works very hard. He deserves ___ a long holiday.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "having", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "to have", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: deserve, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
    },
      {
        question: "He tried to avoid ___ my question.",
        answersList: [
          {answer: "to answer", isCorrect: false},
          {answer: "answering", isCorrect: true},
        ],
        help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: stop, recommend, admit, avoid, imagine, finish, consider, deny, risk, fancy etc'
    },
      {
        question: "The wall was quite high, but the cat managed ___ over it.",
        answersList: [
          {answer: "climbing", isCorrect: false},
          {answer: "to climb", isCorrect: true},
        ],
        help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: manage, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
    },
  ]
export default quiz2data
